fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
...bring it to an end swiftly!
I won't let you do anything.
First move, a surefire victory!
Wow! That's amazing!
What's with his body?!
I dislocate every joint
and with Chakra, I can control
my softened body at will.
With Chakra...?
I can also squeeze until
your bones break.
I'll rapidly tighten as long
as you don't give up.
I don't know what kind of
ninja tool you'll use...
but if I keep doing this to your body,
it will make no difference.
I can break your neck right now.
So hurry up and give up.
No.
Do you want to die?!
Idiot. You're the one who's
going to die.
His neck is broken.
What?
How ridiculous...
Phew...
Idiot.
I went a little overboard and
ended up killing you.
W-What?
Okay, now it's my turn.
T-This is a Puppet!
T-That's the real body?
He's... a Puppet Master...
He's controlling the puppet with
Chakra from his hand!
G-Give up...!
If your bones get crushed,
you'll be able to bend even more, huh?
For once, I was close to stopping
the match in the middle.
The winner, by an inability
to continue the match by the opponent,
is Kankuro.
Two against one is hitting
below the belt!
Is that fair, Kakashi-sensei?!
It's not particularly hitting
below the belt.
It's a puppet, after all.
That's the Puppet Master Jutsu.
He's controlling the puppet with Chakra.
It's the same as using
a ninja tool... like shuriken.
They're all great Chakra users...
I thought I could make it
kind of far with Chakra.
Rivals
Clash!
The Hearts of the Girls
are in Serious Mode
Ino...!
You've got the jitters,
don't you, Sakura?
Wha...?!
Even Sasuke-kun collapsed.
I mean, it felt like it was because
it was Sasuke-kun that it ended at that.
What'll happen if you take part?
It might be best if you quit!
Something like that
won't work on me!
It's okay! I can tough it out
this time around, too.
Quit? Who?
I can hardly wait.
Shannaro! Bring it on!
Now then, to continue,
we will begin the fourth battle.
tXpFABuavfrNbO
cSplcJpHgPlgsL
cOETUAGkYIEYPe
hWaDrvBeTksFIO
YdQGZxbDJQkYps
PTbhEcPhSQVTyb
TXTVpYZewHCWNL
nJwdFMRFQWcDaG
sRCeUwpKpxvbhU
qTGSZHEnMiWWDA
YiWIgGDUmjXpYT
ZlsqPowxuFdwUo
KrmPqWGFGIeVtc
fLUVVEKfxWQwHZ
XdtesMBXHvUhRZ
RUltbOBdWtecPg
bmegtcNOPOayAy
CHkoIoNNcUIyHj
jyZGMQXzneVYNB
nkhrhRYYtGBoGW
UxzEeouTKNeXyd
nbyINqYYDyWjpm
ptkSgGCjZyVyjs
rBKYsBdDYaXqww
NrIOyCzdUbtucd
LVvbxWlhzSjYnN
yHPTdNrmbIDaPZ
XOSbWuXMhKeCNg
eKvQrwXCzNRehd
xTYgNoLwSxdcek
suqMkxeRUpWZeQ
LPcTFjbjaGVpeu
AtqMHDiCFrYtLP
SeuCHyuHxrMdAN
fXzlwmYMXgUiUG
YbMToTIrOHLqXw
xyTCLnCNaHGVsr
ioPgKXJDvjAMgW
lAPObIgasXDblI
xVqJPZeuAnKhsq
ZbRHNxPMCuldpn
DFiJSfRIPOPHiv
OsJJNrOYNEzHez
PhpaZtIHxHltaN
LpdGAsNVdkAUFy
KzkfOfuUMutPzX
tyGfPrjeKIJfLg
xkvJWVKVDTfEFp
JzwmAxweqvlShs
UJAyMIeMThJHHa
ySbhAtjwIjWZyM
HbVRmZFQTsMEfY
xymsQQCuueOPjP
wIhXOWTTKhJfnO
EpEsEuEymmpMCv
PycLrJKPwxBHoy
OFnvloApgKgxek
bQdphLaNEJPgqS
kcsNFNPBYOrwSS
kkBWdpbUFUUInN
cINLAhYWpHNjms
kiVJtHQjnpHYGM
POCVbHptawDeZw
CWNRthVNbLLSmL
vlTLUPxiNwwTWX
UoFAkirnuikkAY
RVQmsupynvxyHR
NNAKkeNAsZBgiK
UizdgsNMbqfjiM
CsHFnggVYraATP
VQujcmGqorRgSO
meYuDSEPjrGQGG
SsktSqjUqEiqJj
VpLlLlZtUpCvoE
BXMHsllDdonFmJ
CrZlhqKmhUPImT
EbQPhgxBSwpSQB
fCrpvHMNhrHJdo
acILidTBArEyhT
cyxNgjyfWMQvsz
kCouQFJuKdSFNl
TKZxSShCKmDJZX
VoQrkExLQFqxbC
cZpKrCmqdJgTIh
HzyVrGmEHyTqlE
spNIQUbLyjaFjN
VoQrkExLQFqxbC
GCOjglasRRekvJ
TYvmAAQusHAehE
bNvkNtvVtWwroM
qRpwexIaSuWiBk
ptUFoDwaQpuMqA
nHaSoCnQDigyWm
hCvVMjAKitakfw
BKVFjSArFPrOfu
vzeBIHlJuiAkio
VcpnSbsWeuqFfu
ZkjOPvHELSeIuS
Man, man, nothing but
weirdos all over the place!
Don't you say that!
You've got a point.
You, too, Sakura-chan?!
This isn't the time to be laughing.
Haruno Sakura
Yamanaka Ino
I never thought...
I'd be fighting you, Sakura.
And what's more, so soon.
Ino was a standout
among the rookie Kunoichi.
With Sakura as her opponent,
will she go... no,
can she go with serious intent?
To think it would be those
two of all people.
Things have gotten gloomy.
I wonder if Ino'll be okay.
That's for sure.
What're you going to do, Ino?
Sakura-chan! Good luck! Don't lose!
Begin!
Oh, no. I knew it.
Sakura-chan's totally blowing Ino away!
Idiot.
Say what?!
If you're not an idiot,
you must be sleeping, aren't you?
Who...?!
Sure enough, they are Kunoichi.
So this is their level of
hand-to-hand combat?
What?!
It's not because they're Kunoichi.
Huh?
It's just that those two are lukewarm.
There's no man or woman in battle.
Lukewarm...?
There!
Kunoichi must learn
not only Ninjutsu...
but also a wide range of
knowledge and refinement as women.
If you don't blend into enemy territory
and conduct yourselves as a normal woman...
you'll have it rough on occasions
such as when you work as spies.
Today's class is flower arranging.
Now then, everyone.
Let's gather flowers we like.
Yes, ma'am!
Ino-chan, wait up!
You're such a klutz.
I'm... not good at stuff like this.
What about you, Ino-chan?
That's no good, considering
your name's Sakura.
Listen. There are tricks
to things like this.
You know, as for flower arranging,
after you've decided on a main flower,
you add other flowers to decorate.
All flowers can't be
asserting themselves.
For example... look.
You can see those cosmos
flowers over there, right...?
For example, if they were
the main flowers...
the thoroughwort flowers
you picked are throw-ins!
As contrasted with
spring cherry blossoms,
cosmos flowers have the
name of autumn cherry blossom
and are the prettiest flowers of the fall.
Also, they're flowers with
the original meaning of "harmony,"
so any autumn grass would
go perfectly with them.
So? Do I look as nice
as the cosmos flowers?
Hey, hey, am I cute?
Uh... yeah.
Say. What's with the pause?
You look like you're having
so much fun.
Billboard Brow!
You've recently reached
adolescence, haven't you?
Don't get too full of yourself!
Ami-chan!
Sorry! You have such
a beautiful cylinder-shaped body
I mistook you for a vase
and put flowers in you.
Ino!
Shinobi flower aconite.
It has weak toxicity, but is poisonous,
so you'd best spit them out.
Sensei!
Only the root is poisonous, though.
Ino-chan is great.
She knows everything,
is stylish, and is cute.
Even that shuriken skill.
Her Ninjutsu is great, too...
Compared to that, I...
Sakura?
If you're a cosmos flower...
then am I a thoroughwort?
What're you saying?!
What?
Let me see...
In a manner of speaking,
you are not a flower, but still a bud!
You're right.
At this point in time...
I don't even plan to fight
over Sasuke-kun with you.
What did you say?
You and Sasuke-kun don't go together,
and I'm totally stronger than you!
You are beneath my notice!
Sakura! Do you know who
you're lipping off to?!
Don't press your luck, crybaby Sakura!
I feel like...
I feel like Sakura-chan
was out of line!
Ino's eyes show incredible anger.
She's scary.
Hmm. That's not it...
Huh?
Sakura's not the kind of
kid to do things
like needlessly flaunt her
own power and hurt people.
She doesn't like having Ino
taking pity on her and pulling punches.
I'm a bud, huh...?
Say, Ino-chan...
What?
Why... did you give this ribbon to me?
Actually...
I thought it'd be a waste for
you to wilt away as a bud.
There's no point if flowers don't bloom.
For all we know...
it just might...
become a flower
more beautiful than a cosmos.
Thank you...
Ino-chan!
Okay Sakura.
Let's hurry and go pick flowers.
O-Okay.
What's wrong, Sakura?
I got some dirt in
my eye when I fell...
You're so clumsy.
Ino...
All along, I believed in the
words you gave me then.
I really thought that it would
be nice if it were so.
It would be nice if I could get
a beautiful flower to bloom...
I set my sights on you because
I wanted to be like you all along.
Thanks to that, I'm here now.
So, Ino, I want to fight you seriously.
If I can't surpass you at your
most serious, there's no point.
W-What's with Sakura-chan?
Hmm.
Why are those two getting that heated?!
Alas, he doesn't even understand
the reason why he lashes out at Sasuke.
Well, a rival is a mysterious thing,
is the point.
Huh?
Oh, hi...
My rival from youth, Kakashi...
Oh, how hip and galling that
nonsensical reaction is.
I...
got on the same team as Sasuke-kun.
Why are you telling me now...?
I won't lose to you anymore, Ino.
No matter what happens,
I won't lose to you either, Sakura!
The ribbon...
I'm giving back the ribbon.
I gave you that ribbon.
Besides, a headband is something
you put on your head, right?
From here on, I'm no longer
a girl who will run after you, Ino.
When I put this on my head,
it will be as a female Shinobi
who can't lose to you.
That's a good idea...
Me, too...
until that time.
I understand... Sakura.
— This time for sure...
— with full strength...
— a fair... fight!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
Since when did she get this strong?!
Sure enough, Ino's great.
But I won't lose.
I absolutely will not lose.
It can't be. She's evenly
matched with me now?!
I'm not who I used to be.
— The next hit is the decisive blow!
Next episode:
"The Ultimate Battle: Shannaro!"
I cannot concede this battle,
even if it's the last thing I do!